My face has some really strange characteristics.
Everyone thinks they've just seen me somewhere.
You're stereotypical.
Similar to many others.
For good or bad?
For spies, it's probably quite
good, but for a diplomat,
that's apparently not good. You
need to have memorable faces.
And for soldiers?
For our military forces, for
our military personnel, it
is now absolutely essential to have strong legs.
And how about his head, then?
What do our heads have to do with
it? They do the thinking for us.
We just carry out orders. Legs are
important. Legs to get away in time.
Aren't you afraid to talk like that to a stranger?
So what, you don't know what my name is.
It is very easy to identify. Because
you have a very memorable face.
Is that so? Oh, damn it. I honestly always
believed my face was just the most common,
the most average one. But even so, it
doesn't really matter. Until you report me,
until a second witness is found. Time
will pass and it will be over. We'll be
put in the dock by them, not the us. And
first and foremost, you the diplomats.
You were killing. You were destroying.
You were burning. And they will judge us?
We were carrying out orders. The SS
were the ones burning. We were fighting.
Did they invent a new way to fight
without destruction or loss of life?
War is one way or another a necessity; not such
a foolish one, of course, this is a diletant's
war. He decided that one could wage war, not by
training at an academy, but purely by intuition.
He decided that he alone truly knows what all
of us need. He decided that he alone loves great
Germany, and all we do is think about how to
sell it to the filthy Bolshevik Cossack kikes.
What's that?
Cossack kikes, that's something
new. I haven't heard that before.
Oh, you can expect anything from the
Reds, but also from the Americans. I've
been fighting them for a year. These
fools will be destroyed by their very
own technology. They think that a war
can be won by bombing alone. *Prost!*
They will build up their technical might and be
overwhelmed by it. It will corrode them like rush.
They will decide that they can
do whatever they please. The reds
think this way because they are wild,
impoverished people. Americans think
this way because they are simply too rich.
Therefore, wars are absolutely necessary.
No connection.
What?
I'm telling you, there's no connection.
Something in your argument is falling apart.
Nothing is falling apart. Nations are just like
people. They simply cannot stand stagnation. The
borders are suffocating them. They need
movement. That's an axiom. Movement is
war. But if you damn diplomats mess up again,
then they will destroy every last one of you.
We were simply following orders. We are soldiers
just like you are, soldiers of the Fuehrer.
Oh, stop pretending, will you?
You're the Fuehrer's soldiers.
A lowranking man who stole a general's boots.
I'm afraid to speak with you, General.
Don't lie. All of Germany is speaking just
like me. Or at least they're thinking it.
And and uh what about those boys from the Hitler
youth when they are sent against the Russian
tanks? Do they also think there are are they
dying with the words Heil Hitler on their lips?
Fanaticism will never achieve a final
victory. People grow weary of fanaticism.
And then this very same fanaticism dissolves
into the thoughts and patterns of behavior
of the defeated. Fanatics might win
in the early stages, but they will
never truly hold on to victory because they
will eventually tire of themselves. *Prost!*
Just then why on earth aren't
you moving your division?
A corps.
All the more reason why won't
you surrender with your corps.
And the family? And what about the the
fanatics at headquarters and the cowards
who'd rather fight believing in a mythical
victory than be turned in an allied camp.
But you can order.
An order is to die. There are no orders
yet to live by surrendering to the enemy.
No army in the world has
learned to write such commands.
What if you get such an order?
From whom? From this neurotic? He's dragging every
single one of us down to the grave. It's truly
terrifying to die when you're all alone. But in
a group, it's nothing. You can even make a joke.
What if Keitel gives you that order?
He's got an ass for a head. He's
a secretary, not a military man.
Well, all right then. Your
commander-in-chief is in Italy.
Kesselring? He would never
agree to something like that.
Why is that?
He was brought up within Goering's headquarters.
But anyone who works under the command of such a
leader is bound to lose their initiative.
They acquire a certain dexterity. They
become a skilled analyst. But they lose the
crucial ability to make their own independent
decisions. He before making a decision on such
a step will absolutely have to fly to the Boar.
To whom? Towards the Boar. Towards Goering.
Are you convinced Kesselring can't be persuaded
to take this step without Goering's approval?
If I weren't convinced, I wouldn't say.
So you don't see a future?
I believe in the future
in the prospect of an impending doom. All of us,
the whole entire group. It's not frightening,
believe me, when we are all united together...
and our destruction would be so utterly
devastating that the memory of it will
deeply wound the hearts of many more
generations of unfortunate Germans.
I have made my final will and
testament for my children. May
every single form of democracy
be utterly cursed throughout
our entire Reich. Any democracy in our
country is fraught with only one thing.
Dictatorship of petty traders.
The more freedoms we have, the
sooner we crave stability,..
secret police, concentration camps,
and widespread universal fear. Only
then do we truly feel at peace.
(Then) you don't need to defend your own
points of view few regarding the fate of the
motherland. Absolutely no responsibility. Just
just raise your hand in honor of the one who's
doing it for you. Just shout Heil Hitler
and everything will be perfectly clear.
No agitation.